# HELLO

I am an interaction designer who believes in thorough research to detail a thoughtful design. I am passionate and skilled at visual design, content strategy and copywriting, which I continuously enhance through academic projects. I strive to marry design with words to communicate the ideas harmoniously.

# EDUCATION

Simon Fraser University 2015 - Present Vancouver, Canada

4th-year design student pursuing BSc in Interactive Arts and Technology.

**Malmö University** 2018 - 2019 Malmö, Sweden

Learned about Swedish design while immersed in a 6-month exchange.

# SKILLS

User experience
User interface
Interaction design
Visual design
Project management

### TOOLS

Sketch
Arduino
Principle
Adobe Creative Suite
Javascript / PHP
HTML / CSS

### ACADEMIC EXPERIENCE

### Interaction designer + Copywriter / Jul 2018

App Re-design for IOS - "Impact Tracker"

Designed an extended function for Share The Meal as a project manager. Decided on design concepts through extensive research on culture and business by reviewing website content and competitors.

Co-created interface for the new feature and formulated copywriting for users to understand the function.

#### Interaction + Visual designer / Nov 2018 - Jan 2019

Smart Clothing Design - "Embodied Emotions"

Developed prototype by conducting observational studies with over 15 users and gauging their experience with materials including plastic and cotton for an interactive garment.

Created visual demonstrations and films to illustrate the function with regards to context and audience.

# Interaction + Visual designer / Nov 2018 - Jan 2019

Smart Clothing Design - "Embodied Emotions"

Developed prototype by conducting observational studies with over 15 users and gauging their experience with materials including plastic and cotton for an interactive garment.

Created visual demonstrations and films to illustrate the function with regards to context and audience.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

### Senior Barista + Trainer Mar 2016 - Jul 2017

Safeway Starbucks

Gained leadership experience by supervising inventory check and new partner training.

Delivered outstanding customer service by providing drink orders in an orderly fashion and effective demonstration of merchandises.

Designed the chalkboard art for weekly drink promotion.

### **VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE**

# Fundraising Assistant June 2019

S.U.C.C.E.S.S. Foundation

Participates in donor relations by managing donation and preparing tax receipt for benefactors through direct mailings.

Referred inquiries and updated the database containing records of donations in office.

Assisted with charity event set-up and guest registration.